

nops **Lode**

Leuven, Belgium

□ (+32)486 62 50 78 | ■ bisschopslode@gmail.com | □ LodeBisschops | □ lode-bisschops

"Without data analytics, companies are blind and deaf, wandering out into the world like deer on a freeway."

Summary.

Current student artificial intelligence at a top university, finishing in July 2022. I'm easy going and love to problem-solve challenging tasks, learn new technologies and interface with different departments. 2+ years of experience interpreting and analyzing data to drive successful business solutions. Excellent knowledge of analytics tools for effective analysis of data.

Work Experience

FibriCheck Hasselt, Belgium DATA ANALYST Feb. 2020 - May 2022

• Created an automated data market using data pipelines and cloud computing infrastructure.

- · Constructed an interactive dashboard with visualisations and filters.
- Provided actionable insights and calculated key performance indicators.
- · Led my own project.
- In depth understanding of NoSQL data aggregation through research.
- Created complex data insights using Python and Jupyter notebooks.
- Interfaced with marketing to understand their needs.
- Clearly documented my work and educated colleagues at the end of my contract.
- Traineeship that turned into permanent employment with the firm.

TeamHypeCoaching Flanders, Belgium

STRENGTH COACH Nov. 2020 - Jun. 2021

- Built up a company with 2 friends, providing online strength coaching for 40 athletes.
- · Progress analysis using excel automation.

Le Notariat Westerlo, Belgium

WAITER AND HOSPITALITY Jun. 2020 - Sep. 2021

• Serving at a Gault & Millau selected cocktail bar, serving guests as a hospitable host.

Education

Katholieke Universiteit Leuven

MASTERS OF COMPUTER SCIENCE: ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE

Leuven, Belgium 2020 - 2022

2016 - 2020

- · Belgium's highest-ranked university.
- · Completing degree in July.

University of Hasselt BACHELORS OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Hasselt, Belgium

• In depth understanding of Python, Java, C++ and C.

- · Strong background in mathematics, statistics and software engineering.
- Familiar with: Prolog, Javascript, cloud based solutions, relational and non-relational databases.
- Familiar with the latest project management techniques.

Research_

MASTER THESIS

Exploring Deceptive affiliate Marketing within Facebook

· Researching malicious advertisements within Facebook and how to detect them.

- Finding patterns within large datasets using SQL, Python and MongoDB.
- · Gathering data with web-scraping tools in remote containerized applications using Kubernetes.

BISSCHOPS LODE · RÉSUMÉ APRIL 20, 2022

Leuven, Belgium

2021 - 2022

Aggregating Data for Statistical Analysis in MongoDB Atlas.

Hasselt, Belgium

Bachelor Thesis Feb. 2020 - Jun. 2020

- Compared different database technologies for data aggregation.
- Explored different ways to aggregate data in an unstructured NoSQL database.
- Set up a real-time dashboard for basic performance indicators.

Extracurricular Activity

Hermes - fraternity of economics

Hasselt, Belgium

2019 - 2020

- PLEDGEMASTER

 Organised social events for new students.
- Assisted the job fair.
- Participated in biweekly meetings.

References_

Ine Van Loon, Marketing Manager, *FibriCheck*, ■ ine.vanloon@fibricheck.com Glenn De Witte, Data Science Manager, *FibriCheck*, ■ glenn.dewitte@fibricheck.com Guylian Menten, Owner, *Le Notariat*, □(+32) 493 13 73 88

Reference letters can be viewed on https://lodebisschops.com/references/.